where do you put up is a hot dog burger
Wow
welcome to dreary San Francisco is there
any more toys oh no there's no Wi-Fi
outside we're only gonna be here for a
minute we can look up at the commentary
this is the calm a Labor Day celebration
we put charcoal in the gas grill who did
that
we cooked burgers and hot dogs and beer
and vegetarian food there's not much to
say in the scope II accept two things
one midnight black eons are only on sale
from those six hours make sure to go buy
some too
if you had work today
congratulations you have a real job and
three don't forget about the video
contest we'll be judging it on the ninth
so get your open pilot videos together
we'll all be judging it will be a joint
they'll be like the American Idol
for videos thank you for joining scope
ease I hope you have a great Labor Day
and that's Labor with an O are not a no
you are like the Brits might say so what
Labor Day with oh you is another time
yeah yeah doesn't May yeah yeah they
have like but like in America is like
afraid of Communists so confuse that
with made it yeah that sounds communist
we're afraid of them is America fastest
copies do the video do the video earn
$1,000 and go buy midnight black peons
while you still the chance to see if
it's crazy low price
and refer your friends oh yeah yeah I
mean that's what these things really are
um
affiliate all affiliate link like that I
was thinking if you want to come work at
coming I we're hiring two people we're
hiring a test engineer and the machine
learning engineer I had a full stack
engineer I'm so if you're interested
give me a job Akane I and you could join
things like our great Labor Day a deuce
be challenge yeah if you're ml juice be
a challenge the other two just like be
good we're Kearney Mazda has puppies
that buys job
[Music]